[{"answer": "Aye, ma'am", "docId": "mrs_brown.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "I am", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "So, there are rules.  Things you do and things you don't do", "docId": "mrs_brown.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "You don't tell Her Majesty how you feel", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Go inside at once", "docId": "mrs_brown.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Yes, it most certainly is", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": " No dinners, my friend.  Why are you dressed for outdoors", "docId": "mrs_brown.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Cold is goo", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Excellent, ma'am, excellent.  But perhaps if her Majesty were to consider accompanying her ne", "docId": "mrs_brown.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Forgive me, Your Majesty.  In no way did I wish to sugges", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": " I do not do it for others.  But my friend thinks they are good", "docId": "mrs_brown.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": " Of course I shall say what I have to say.  I always do", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Surely it is for the gentlemen to decide when to stop..", "docId": "mrs_brown.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Yes, but isn't midnight a little excessive", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "What's her excuse this time", "docId": "mrs_brown.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "I was trying to imagine", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Convey her a message", "docId": "mrs_brown.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Tell her the Prince of that place wishes to speak with her urgently about matters concerning the press", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "I said, are you deaf as well as stupid", "docId": "mrs_brown.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Whom you address", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Then they may read about me", "docId": "mrs_brown.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Is that not enough", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Dare say you can be taught", "docId": "mrs_brown.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "If you hunt, you kill", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Back and upper corridors", "docId": "mrs_brown.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Front door.  Checked and locked", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "They don't see it", "docId": "mrs_brown.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "The threat.  I tell them, but they don't see it", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "The greasy pole", "docId": "mrs_brown.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "No love", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Prince my friend is at that place, ma'am", "docId": "mrs_brown.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "He is sick, ma'am", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Why is he not here", "docId": "mrs_brown.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Then why are you not with him", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "You should never have gone out in such foul weather", "docId": "mrs_brown.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Yes.  Yes it was", "qsentId": 36}]